Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council Records 5254
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council Records
1939-1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council
5254
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection contains the office files of the Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council from its organization in 1937 to their merger with the Buffalo Federation of Labor in 1958. Include general administrative records, materials relating to labor legislation, relations with member organizations, relations with New York State Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) and the national CIO, relations with international labor organizations and with the public.
3833886
Biographical / Historical
Local industrial union councils operated on a city, county, or district basis and were composed of the CIO local unions within these areas. The industrial union councils were under the control of the CIO, but the CIO did not force its nationals and internationals to make their local unions join the local councils. The Local councils, like the state councils, were coordinating agencies designed to serve the local unions within their area.
"The objects of the Council shall be to secure united action of all locals of national and international unions and organizing committees and local industrial unions and industrial union councils affiliated to the CIO within its jurisdiction and through united action to protect, maintain and advance the interests of all working people in its territory, to extend unionism on the basis of industrial organization, to secure and enforce legislation in the interests of the working people, to promote recognition and acceptance of collective bargaining in industry, and to increase public understanding of the labor movement."
-CIO Model Constitution
The Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council was organized in 193T. The council participated in organizing work and engaged in politics: municipal, state and national. It tried to cultivate a favorable public opinion toward CIO unions. The council sometimes engaged in various types of educational work, such as forming study classes and encouraged the formation of education committees in local unions.
Scope and Contents
Include general administrative records, materials relating to labor legislation, relations with member organizations, relations with New York State Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) and the national CIO, relations with international labor organizations and with the public.
General administrative records (1938-1958) include correspondence, publications, resolutions, reports, minutes and ballots concerning the sentiment of the GBIUC on various state and federal legislative proposals, political endorsements, veterans' affairs, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations relations, local strikes, and various other local union matters. Specific issues covered in these records include employment stabilization after World War II; unemployment insurance and workmen's compensation; industrial safety and hygiene; jurisdictional disputes and raiding between the Niagara, N.Y. locals of the United Automobile Workers and the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers; strikes at Remington Rand, Bell Aircraft, and the National Carbon Company; and the merger of American Federation of Labor (A.F. of L.) and Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) unions in Buffalo.
A resolutions file (1939-1958) includes matters coming before the GBIUC for its endorsement or opposition. These include proposed new or amended federal, state, or county legislation and public issues of interest to organized labor. Among the issues acted upon were the Hatch-Ball-Burton Bill, S.1171; a national health bill; the Taft-Hartley Act, the St. Lawrence power project; time-and-a-half provisions for county workers; and the imposition of state sales tax in New York. The GBIUC also expressed its opinion on the issues of runaway shops, social security, unemployment, a guaranteed annual wage, slum clearance and low rent housing, World War II defense issues, and the anti-communist campaign of the 1950's, among others.
The collection contains files relating to the Council's relations with its member organizations, including correspondence, reports, resolutions, surveys, legislative materials, and publications (1939-1959). These records concern financial matters, and affiliated local activities, including strikes, contract negotiations, and arbitration. Also included is a survey of the thirty-five affiliated member organizations on the impact of post World War II reconversion and employment.
GBIUC relations with the New York State CIO Council are documented in resolutions, reports and correspondence between the two organizations. Discussed are right-to-work laws, the New York State Disability Benefits Law, a rent control bill, unemployment insurance, and workmen's compensation, among other issues.
The Council's varied political activities are recorded throughout the collection but particularly in its legislative action files (1940-1959). These include correspondence, resolutions, legislative materials, statements, and surveys. Municipal correspondents include Bernard J. Dowd (mayor of Buffalo), Francis E. Franczak (Buffalo Department of Health), and Leo J. Hagerty (district attorney, Erie County) as well as officials of the Buffalo Common Council, the Buffalo Policemen's Organization, the Buffalo Port Authority, the City of Lackawanna, the Erie County Board of Supervisors and County Department of Social Welfare. New York State correspondents include Stanley J. Bauer (senator), Frederick T. Devlin (assistant attorney general), Charles W. Halloran (acting industrial commissioner, Department of Labor), Averell Harriman (governor), and Walter J. Mahoney (senator), as well as other representatives of the State Assembly, Department of Labor, and Public Services Commission. National legislative correspondents include Homer E. Capchant (senator), Chester C. Gorski (congressman), Irving M. Ives (senator), Jacob K. Javits (senator), James M. Mead (senator), John R. Pillion (congressman), Edmund P. Radwan (congressman), and Anthony F. Tauriello (congressman).
Subjects discussed in this correspondence include workmen's compensation, the Condon-Wadlin Bill, apprenticeship standards, New York State health and safety legislation, unemployment insurance, anti-discrimination and anti-labor legislation, civil rights, conservation, housing, wage legislation and price control, taxes, social security, the Missouri Valley Authority and the St. Lawrence Seaway project.
Also included in these records are correspondence and other documents relating to the GBIUC's activities with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, labor groups around the world and various Buffalo, N.Y. and regional social organizations (ca. 1940's-1950's).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5407 mf: Random selection of papers from Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council Records on Microfilm
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 29, 2003
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2017
Foreign workers -- United States; Anti-communist movements -- United States; Civil rights -- New York (State); Cost and standard of living -- United States; Employment stabilization -- United States; Guaranteed annual wage -- United States; Hours of labor -- United States; Industrial hygiene -- United States; Industrial safety -- United States; Disability insurance -- New York (State); Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); Labor laws and legislation -- New York (State); Labor laws and legislation -- United States; Sales tax -- New York (State); Social security -- United States; Strikes and lockouts--New York (State); Tax collection -- New York (State); Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Buffalo -- Political activity; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Political activity; Labor unions -- United States -- Political activity; Veterans -- Employment -- United States; Workers' compensation -- New York (State); Housing -- New York (State) -- Law and legislation; Health insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Open and closed shop -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Race discrimination -- Law and legislation -- United States; Runaway shops -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Aircraft industry -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Coal mining industry -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Electronic industries -- United States; Labor unions -- Mergers -- New York (State) -- Buffalo; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Local unions; Labor unions -- Jurisdictional disputes -- New York (State) -- Niagara Falls; Wages -- County employees -- United States; Minimum wage -- United States; Public works -- United States; Bauer, Stanley J.; Capchant, Homer (Homer Earl); Devlin, Frederick T.; Dowd, Bernard J.; Gorski, Chester C.; Harriman, Averell, 1891-1986; Ives, Irving McNeil, 1896-1962.; Javits, Jacob K. (Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986; Mahoney, Walter J., 1908-1982; Mead, James M.; Pillion, John R.; Radwan, E.P. (Edmund P.); Tauriello, Anthony F.; AFL-CIO. Committee on Political Education; Bell Aircraft Company; CIO Council (N.Y.); Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council (CIO); International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (A.F. of L.); International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO); National Carbon Company; New York (State). Department of Labor; New York (State). Legislature. Assembly.; New York State CIO Council; Remington Rand, Inc.; United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America; United States. Labor Management Relations Act, 1947
3833886
- Council Meetings, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Affiliation Statistics, 1941-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Financial - PAC, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Financial - Council Hall, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Financial Reports (monthly), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Executive Board, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dunkerdoings, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Scope and Contents
  Aug. 6th - Nov. 12th
- Disputes - Non-member, 1947-1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Council Meetings, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Council Meetings, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Council Meetings, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Council Meetings, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Council Election, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Financial - Per Capita Revision, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Council Election, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Financial - Per Capita Revision, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Council Election, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Council Election, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Council Election (special for merger candidate), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Convention Reports - Miller, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Constitution - Buffalo Council, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Industrial Union Council Requirements (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Industrial Union Council Constitutions (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Constitutional Committee, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Conference - National CIO Anti-inflation Conference, Miller vs. Miller, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Committees - Standing, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Committees - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Building Fund, 1944-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Arbitration Association, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Council Election, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Personnel - Unemployment Insurance (Box 1, Folder 45)
- War Manpower Commission Procedure (Box 1, Folder 59)
- War Manpower Commission Newsclippings (Box 1, Folder 58)
- War Manpower Commission Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Veterans, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Veterans, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Veterans, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Veterans - On-the-job Training (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Union Label (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Strike Communications, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Strike Communications, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Safety (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Press Releases, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Financial - Per Capita, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Personnel - Workmen's Compensation (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Union Leader, 1950-1958 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Personnel - Severence Pay (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Personnel - Employee Bonds (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Personnel - Employee Agreement, 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Newsclipping Scrapbook, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Organizational Report, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- New York City - CIO Newspaper, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  April 23rd - Oct. 29th
- Miller - Personal (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Merger (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Labor Education (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Labor Day Speeches (Box 1, Folder 35)
- I.U.C. Controversy (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Industrial Union Councils, 1946-1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Financial - Ways & Means Comm., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Press Releases, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Resolutions, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Resolutions, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Community and Social Agency Employees (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Communications Workers (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Buffalo Teachers Union - U.P.W. (Box 2, Folder 21)
- American Newspaper Guild - Buffalo, Local 26 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Lithographers (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers Locals 201, 207, 213, & 237 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Resolutions, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Resolutions, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Resolutions, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Federal Labor Unions (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Resolutions, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Food, Tobacco, and Agricultural Workers (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Resolutions, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Resolutions, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Resolutions, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Resolutions, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Resolutions, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Resolutions, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Resolutions, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Resolutions, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Policy Statement, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Resolutions - updated - WWII (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Resolutions, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (Box 2, Folder 37)
- United Auto Workers, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- United Auto Workers, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- United Auto Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Transport Workers (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Textile Workers (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Strike - Bell Aircraft, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Stone and Allied Workers (Box 2, Folder 43)
- State, County, and Municipal Workers (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Retail - Wholesale Workers (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Playthings, Jewelry, and Novelty Workers (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Farm Equipment & Metal Workers (Box 2, Folder 24)
- National Maritime Union (Box 2, Folder 38)
- United Auto Workers, 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Local Union Officers Lists, 1946-1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Local Union Reconversion and Unemployment Survey, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  September
- Local Union Contract Survey II, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  January
- Local Union Contract Survey I, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Local Unions - Communications to (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Local Union Agreements (Box 2, Folder 31)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (Box 2, Folder 30)
- International Fur and Leather Workers, Local 39 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Glass, Ceramic, and Silica Sand Workers (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Optical and Instrument Workers (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Utility Workers (Box 3, Folder 12)
- United Brewery Workers (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Legislative Program, N.Y. State CIO, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- United Rubber Workers (Box 3, Folder 15)
- N.Y. State CIO Council - Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1949-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- CIO Reporter- N.Y. Council, 1945-1952 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- United Railway Workers (Box 3, Folder 11)
- United Public Workers (Box 3, Folder 10)
- United Paper Workers (Box 3, Folder 9)
- United Packinghouse Workers (Box 3, Folder 8)
- United Office and Professional Workers (Box 3, Folder 7)
- United Heater Equipment Workers (Box 3, Folder 6)
- United Furniture Workers Locals 37, 39, & 103 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (Box 3, Folder 4)
- United Construction Workers (Box 3, Folder 3)
- United Chemical Workers Locals 85, 215, & 375 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Publications - N.Y. State CIO Counsel (Box 3, Folder 37)
- General Correspondence with National CIO, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- General Correspondence with National CIO, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- General Correspondence with National CIO, 1948-1951 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Financial Reports, AFL-CIO (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Conference - National Win the Peace Conference, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Conference - National CIO Anti-inflation Conference, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- AFL-CIO No Raiding, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Conference - National AFL-CIO Economic and Legislative Conference, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Conference - National AFL-CIO COPE Conference, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- CIO Region II, Director (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Constitution, N.Y. State CIO Counsel (Box 3, Folder 24)
- N.Y. State CIO Council - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- General Correspondence with National CIO, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- PAC - N.Y. State CIO (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Legislative Report, N.Y. State CIO, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- COPE - Notes and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Newsclippings, N.Y. State CIO (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Convention - Merger, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Convention - N.Y. State CIO, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Convention - N.Y. State CIO, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Convention - N.Y. State CIO, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Convention - N.Y. State CIO, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- CIO Reporter - N.Y. Council, 1955-1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- N.Y. State CIO Council - Correspondence, 1945-1954 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- National CIO Community Services Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- PAC - Memo from PAC, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- PAC - Memo from PAC, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- PAC, National CIO II (Box 4, Folder 19)
- PAC, National CIO I (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Legislation, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Legislation, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- National CIO Education & Research Dept, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- National CIO Education & Research Dept, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Reports on Congress, National CIO Legislative Dept, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Murray, Philip (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Foreign Visitors, 1953-1958 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Policy - National CIO, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Policy - National CIO, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Policy- National CIO, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- National Convention, CIO, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- National Convention, CIO, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Industrial Union Councils, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Industrial Union Councils, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Reports on Congress, National CIO Legislative Dept, 1946-1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reports on Congress, National CIO Legislative Dept., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- National CIO Education & Research Dept, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Musicians (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Office Employees (Box 4, Folder 44)
- N.Y. State Federation of Labor (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Longshoremen (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Local Independent Unions (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Joint Labor Committee (Box 4, Folder 40)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Canadian Seamens Union (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Buffalo Federation of Teachers (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Buffalo Federation of Labor, John J. Higgins (Box 4, Folder 36)
- PAC- Pipeline, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Barbers and Beauty Culturists (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Europe - Anthony Luchek, CIO European Representative, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- World Trade - U.S. Department of State (Box 4, Folder 32)
- World Federation of Trade Unions - Information Bulletin (Box 4, Folder 31)
- World Federation of Trade Unions (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Latin American Federation of Labor (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Jewish Labor Committee (Box 4, Folder 28)
- International Labor Conditions (Box 4, Folder 27)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Histadrut, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Strike - Relief (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Sales Tax (Box 5, Folder 13)
- American Labor Party - Central Clubs (Box 5, Folder 1)
- PAC - Bulletins (Box 5, Folder 24)
- PAC, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- PAC, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- PAC, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- PAC, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- PAC, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- PAC, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Main - Humboldt Underpass (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Health (Box 5, Folder 16)
- PAC - Buffalo Community Platform Municipal Elections, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- United Labor Committee of the Tonawandas (Box 5, Folder 14)
- PAC - Endorsement Requests, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  May to June
- Rybka, Peter - Councilman, Buffalo (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Parking Meters (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hagerty, Leo J, - District Attorney, Erie County (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Fronczak, Dr. Francis E. - Department of Health (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Erie County Department of Social Welfare (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Erie County Board of Supervisors (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Dowd, Bernard J. - Mayor of Buffalo (Box 5, Folder 6)
- City of Lackawanna (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Buffalo Port Authority (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Policemen's Organization (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Common Council (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Wendling, Frank - Erie County Supervisor (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Halloran, Charles W. - N.Y. State Department (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Unemployment Insurance (Box 5, Folder 51)
- State Income Tax (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Safety (Box 5, Folder 49)
- New York State Commission on the Constitutional Convention, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- New York State Apprenticeship Council (Box 5, Folder 47)
- New York State Public Service Commission (Box 5, Folder 46)
- New York State Department of Labor (Box 5, Folder 45)
- New York State Assembly (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Minimum Wage (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Mahoney, Walter J. - State Senator, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 42)
- PAC - Convention, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Harriman, Averell - Governor, N.Y. State (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Workmen's Compensation (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Gasoline Sign Restrictions (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Dewey, Thomas E. - Governor, N.Y. State (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Devlin, Frederick T. - Assistant Attorney General, N.Y. State (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Bauer, Stanley J. - State Senator, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Anti-discrimination (Box 5, Folder 34)
- PAC - Workers, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- PAC - Hillery & Lehman Campaigns (Box 5, Folder 32)
- PAC - Endorsement Requests, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- PAC - Endorsement Requests, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- PAC - Endorsement Requests, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  August to November
- PAC - Endorsement Requests, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  July
- Legislation (general) N.Y. State (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Conservation (Box 6, Folder 8)